ACTWU Collective Bargaining Agreements 5619/001
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Chicago Joint Board and Bublick & Holland, Inc. and S.J. Stores, Inc., 1973-1976 (Box 128, Folder 7)
- New York Joint Board and Louis Caruso, 1977 (Box 128, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Central Coat Apron & Linen Service, Inc., 1975 (Box 128, Folder 9)
- Cleveland Joint Board and Charles, Ltd., 1986 (Box 128, Folder 10)
- New York Joint Board and Charles II Clothes, Ltd., 1978 (Box 128, Folder 11)
- Boston Joint Board and Charlesgate Clothes, Inc., 1974-1977 (Box 128, Folder 12)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and Chipp Custom Tailors of New Haven, 1965-1977 (Box 128, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Clover Laundry, Inc., 1975 (Box 128, Folder 14)
- Northern California Joint Board and Colshire of California, Inc., 1960-1972 (Box 128, Folder 15)
- Chicago Joint Board and Community Discount Centers, Inc., 1967-1975 (Box 128, Folder 16)
- New York Joint Board and Concept I, 1978-1981 (Box 128, Folder 17)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Concord Laundry, 1975 (Box 128, Folder 18)
- New Jersey, Local #195 and Cornwalls, Inc., 1980 (Box 128, Folder 19)
- New York Joint Board and Cricket Shop of Cedarhurst, Inc., 1981 (Box 128, Folder 20)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and Cripp's Clothes of Hartford, 1959-1971 (Box 128, Folder 21)
- Midwest Regional Joint Board, Local #3 and Curtis Fashion Bar, Inc., 1970-1973 (Box 128, Folder 22)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and Ken Davis of Hartford, 1959-1968 (Box 128, Folder 23)
- Massachusetts, Local #377 and Delton Shirtmakers, Inc., 1973 (Box 128, Folder 24)
- New England Regional Joint Board and J.L. DeMichele, Ltd., 1971-1976 (Box 128, Folder 25)
- Southern California Joint Board and Sy Devore, Inc., 1977-1980 (Box 128, Folder 26)
- Chicago Joint Board and William Diamond, Inc., 1964 (Box 128, Folder 27)
- New England Tailors Joint Board and Dino's Clothes, Inc., 1965-1977 (Box 128, Folder 28)
- Chicago Joint Board and Discount Clothing, Inc., 1972-1973 (Box 128, Folder 29)
- Chicago Joint Board, Local #215 and Dizon's Men's Wear, 1977 (Box 128, Folder 30)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Dubarry Private Hand Laundry, Inc., 1975 (Box 128, Folder 31)
- Capitol District Joint Board, Local #7 and Dan A. Donahue, Inc., 1974-1977 (Box 128, Folder 32)
- New York Joint Board, Local #162 and Dornan, Inc., 1980 (Box 128, Folder 33)
- New York Joint Board and Dorson Clothes Co., 1978-1981 (Box 128, Folder 34)
- Chicago Joint Board and E-Ton, Inc., 1975 (Box 128, Folder 35)
- International Glove Workers Union, Local #83 and Eisendrath Glove Co., 1960-1963 (Box 128, Folder 36)
- New York Joint Board and Enrico Clothes, Inc., 1978-1981 (Box 128, Folder 37)
- Chicago Joint Board and Erie Clothing Co., 1969 (Box 128, Folder 38)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and Erlanger's Men's Clothes of Waterbury, 1965-1971 (Box 128, Folder 39)
- Chicago Joint Board and Esquire Joe's, 1973-1976 (Box 128, Folder 40)
- New York Joint Board and European Tailor Shop, Inc., 1979 (Box 128, Folder 41)
- Chicago Joint Board and Fair Drug Co., Inc., 1965-1975 (Box 128, Folder 42)
- New York, Local #340A and Famous Fashion Shops, Ltd., 1970 (Box 128, Folder 43)
- Chicago Joint Board and Fashion Plate, Inc., 1973 (Box 128, Folder 44)
- Capitol District, Local #7 and Fashion Tailors, 1977-1985 (Box 128, Folder 45)
- New York Joint Board and Fashions for Men, 1980-1982 (Box 128, Folder 46)
- New York Joint Board and Finchley, Inc., 1969-1976 (Box 128, Folder 47)
- New York Joint Board and Fits-U-Custom Tailors, Inc., 1978-1981 (Box 128, Folder 48)
- Midwest Regional Joint Board, Local #3 and Stuart Fitzpatrick, Ltd., 1973-1976 (Box 128, Folder 49)
- New York Joint Board and Formal Den, Ltd., 1971-1981 (Box 128, Folder 50)
- New York Joint Board and Formal Den, Ltd., 1970-1972 (Box 128, Folder 51)
- Chicago Joint Board and Frankfurth Hardware. Co., 1975 (Box 128, Folder 52)
- New York Joint Board and S.K. Friedman & Sons, 1981 (Box 128, Folder 53)
- Chicago Joint Board and Friedman's Men's Shop, Inc., 1977 (Box 128, Folder 54)
- Capitol District, Local #188 and G & G Uniform Co., 1960-1975 (Box 128, Folder 55)
- Boston Joint Board and G.T., Inc., 1975 (Box 128, Folder 56)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries Joint Board and Garden Sanitary Laundry, 1975 (Box 128, Folder 57)
- Capitol District, Local #188 and Garfinckel's, 1962-1983 (Box 128, Folder 58)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and Gentree, Ltd., 1965-1977 (Box 128, Folder 59)
- Chicago Joint Board and Gieringer-Palace, Inc., 1977 (Box 128, Folder 60)
- New York Joint Board and Gilcrest Clothes Co., Inc., 1977-1980 (Box 128, Folder 61)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Gimbels Midwest, Inc., 1965-1984 (Box 128, Folder 62)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Joint Board and Gordon of Philadelphia, 1982 (Box 128, Folder 63)
- Midwest Regional Joint Board, Local #3 and Grassfield's - Gano Downs, 1976 (Box 128, Folder 64)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Greenfield Prescription Center (Union Prescription Centers, Inc.), 1975-1987 (Box 128, Folder 65)
- Chicago Joint Board and Hartfield-Zodys, Inc., 1973-1974 (Box 128, Folder 66)
- New York Joint Board and Harry Halpern & Son, Inc., 1978-1981 (Box 128, Folder 67)
- Boston Joint Board and Hanover Co., Inc., 1975 (Box 128, Folder 68)
- Wisconsin, Local #126-G and Hansen Glove Corp., 1961-1962 (Box 128, Folder 69)
- Wisconsin, Local #130-G and Hansen Glove Corp., 1961-1968 (Box 129, Folder 1)
- New York Joint Board and David Hober, 1977 (Box 129, Folder 2)
- Chicago Joint Board and Hochscheild Tailors, 1980 (Box 129, Folder 3)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and Horsfall's, Inc., 1965-1968 (Box 129, Folder 4)
- New England, Local #579 and Howard Clothes, 1965-1971 (Box 129, Folder 5)
- Boston Joint Board and Howard Clothes, Inc., 1977 (Box 129, Folder 6)
- Chicago Joint Board and Howard Clothes, 1977 (Box 129, Folder 7)
- California Joint Board and The Hub Schneider, 1982 (Box 129, Folder 8)
- New York Joint Board and Hygrade Sportswear, Inc., 1981 (Box 129, Folder 9)
- New York Joint Board and Hy-Rubin Forest Hills, Inc., 1981 (Box 129, Folder 10)
- New York Joint Board and Irving's Fashions for Men, Inc., 1978-1981 (Box 129, Folder 11)
- Chicago Joint Board and J.A. Promotions, 1976 (Box 129, Folder 12)
- Chicago Joint Board and Janicki's Men's Wear, Ltd., 1977 (Box 129, Folder 13)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and J. Johnson-Kennedy's, 1965 (Box 129, Folder 14)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and Jones Morgan-Besse Richey, Inc., 1965-1968 (Box 129, Folder 15)
- New Jersey, Local #195 and Kartch's of Hackensack, 1980 (Box 129, Folder 16)
- Chicago Joint Board and Kassner's California Men's Shop, 1964 (Box 129, Folder 17)
- Chicago Joint Board and Kay's Men's Wear, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 18)
- Chicago Joint Board and Kayes Corp. (Union Prescription Centers), 1975 (Box 129, Folder 19)
- General Office and Kelly Clothes, Inc., 1980 (Box 129, Folder 20)
- Capitol District, Local #7 and Kennedy Clothes, 1977 (Box 129, Folder 21)
- New England Regional Joint Board and Kennedy, Inc., 1977-1990 (Box 129, Folder 22)
- New England Regional Joint Board, Local #115 and Kennedy's, Inc., 1977-1980 (Box 129, Folder 23)
- New York Joint Board and Kenney's, 1978 (Box 129, Folder 24)
- New York Joint Board and Roger Kent, 1976 (Box 129, Folder 25)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and Browning King, Inc., 1962 (Box 129, Folder 26)
- New York Joint Board and Knickerbocher Clothes, 1981 (Box 129, Folder 27)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and Kramer's, Inc., 1965-1968 (Box 129, Folder 28)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Mayer Krom Co. (Robert L. Gove), 1978 (Box 129, Folder 29)
- Chicago Joint Board and L G M Fashions, Inc., 1972 (Box 129, Folder 30)
- Capitol District Joint Board and Lafayette Clothes, Inc., 1977-1987 (Box 129, Folder 31)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Lakes Laundry, Inc., 1975 (Box 129, Folder 32)
- Chicago Joint Board and Leading Man, Inc., 1974-1977 (Box 129, Folder 33)
- Boston Joint Board and Lebow Bros., Inc., 1971-1974 (Box 129, Folder 34)
- New York Joint Board and George Leonard Clothiers, 1981 (Box 129, Folder 35)
- California Joint Board and Leslies Mens Shop, 1983 (Box 129, Folder 36)
- New York Joint Board and Mervin S. Levine Co., 1980-1982 (Box 129, Folder 37)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Carl Liametz Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1985-1986 (Box 129, Folder 38)
- New York Joint Board and Sol Liss Mens Shop, 1981 (Box 129, Folder 39)
- New York Joint Board and Lloyd's, 1983-1984 (Box 129, Folder 40)
- New York Joint Board and Henry Lokos, 1981 (Box 129, Folder 41)
- New York Joint Board and Bob Lorry's, Ltd., 1981 (Box 129, Folder 42)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and J.W. Losse, 1970-1973 (Box 129, Folder 43)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Luetzow Laundry Cleaners (S.D. Nicholas Investment, Inc.), 1982 (Box 129, Folder 44)
- Cleveland Joint Board and Lyon Tailoring, 1977-1982 (Box 129, Folder 45)
- New York Joint Board and M & G Sportswear, 1977 (Box 129, Folder 46)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and M.J. Manufacturing Corp., 1969-1972 (Box 129, Folder 47)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and M.L.M. Sportswear, 1962-1965 (Box 129, Folder 48)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and M.P.L., Inc. (Union Prescription Centers, Inc.), 1982-1987 (Box 129, Folder 49)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board and M&R Manufacturing Corp., 1976 (Box 129, Folder 50)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and Mac-Daid, Inc. of New Haven, 1959-1968 (Box 129, Folder 51)
- Cincinnati Joint Board and MacGregor Sport Products, Inc., 1943-1960 (Box 129, Folder 52)
- Cincinnati Joint Board, Local #200 and Brunswick Sports (MacGregor), 1962-1964 (Box 129, Folder 53)
- Midwest Regional Joint Board, Local #3 and Mack-John's Custom Tailors, 1973-1976 (Box 129, Folder 54)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Magerman Trousers, Inc., 1977 (Box 129, Folder 55)
- New York Joint Board and Magic Fashions, Inc., 1980 (Box 129, Folder 56)
- Midwest Regional Joint Board, Local #3 and Joseph Magnin, 1973 (Box 129, Folder 57)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and Male Box, 1971-1974 (Box 129, Folder 58)
- New York Joint Board and Male Shop, 1981 (Box 129, Folder 59)
- Glove Cities Area Joint Board, Local #1714 and Mansfield Glove, 1969 (Box 129, Folder 60)
- New England Tailors Joint Board and Mark, Inc., 1968-1977 (Box 129, Folder 61)
- New York Joint Board and Sy Mark Tall Towne, Inc., 1981 (Box 129, Folder 62)
- Chicago Joint Board and Marks-Chicago Corp. (Steinberg-Baum), 1972 (Box 129, Folder 63)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and Marshall's Clothes, 1965-1972 (Box 129, Folder 64)
- New York Joint Board and Marsy Clothes, Inc., 1981 (Box 130, Folder 1)
- New England Regional Joint Board and Martini-Carl, Inc., 1969-1980 (Box 130, Folder 2)
- Cleveland Joint Board and the May Co., 1977-1986 (Box 130, Folder 3)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and Mead Clothes, Inc., 1959-1962 (Box 130, Folder 4)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and Meig's & Co., 1968 (Box 130, Folder 5)
- New York Joint Board and Micucci Tailors, Inc., 1977-1982 (Box 130, Folder 6)
- Chicago Joint Board and Midwest Outerwear, Inc., 1972-1976 (Box 130, Folder 7)
- Boston Joint Board and Mr. John, Inc., 1972-1974 (Box 130, Folder 8)
- Chicago Joint Board and Mister Sam's Custom Tailoring, 1970 (Box 130, Folder 9)
- New Jersey, Local #195 and Mr. Stag, Inc., 1980 (Box 130, Folder 10)
- New York Joint Board and Murray Hill Custom Tailors, 1978 (Box 130, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Murray Hill Laundry & Cleaners, Inc., 1975 (Box 130, Folder 12)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and National Pharmacy (Union Prescription Centers, Inc.), 1978-1984 (Box 130, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and National Towel Supply, 1975 (Box 130, Folder 14)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Northern Wire Corp., 1986-1987 (Box 130, Folder 15)
- Capitol District, Local #7 and Jos. Nussbaum, Inc., 1977-1980 (Box 130, Folder 16)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and Nyden's (Johnson & Sons), 1968 (Box 130, Folder 17)
- New York Joint Board and 192-11 Union Turnpike Clothes, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box 130, Folder 18)
- New England Regional Joint Board and Outlet Department Stores, Inc., 1968-1980 (Box 130, Folder 19)
- New England, Local #359 and P & M Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1952-1969 (Box 130, Folder 20)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and Ray Pacific of Trumbull, 1965-1977 (Box 130, Folder 21)
- Boston Joint Board and Wolf Outerwear Co., 1953-1962 (Box 130, Folder 22)
- Chicago Joint Board and Palay's Squire Shop, 1977 (Box 130, Folder 23)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Paramount Custom Tailors, 1977-1983 (Box 130, Folder 24)
- Chicago Joint Board and Paramount-Washington Co. (The Lelewer Store for Men), 1971-1974 (Box 130, Folder 25)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers' Union and Parkley Shirt Co., Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 130, Folder 26)
- New England Tailors' Joint Board and Peerless-Eastfield Co., 1977 (Box 130, Folder 27)
- Massachusetts, Local #579 and Rogers Peet Co., 1961 (Box 130, Folder 28)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and Rogers Peet Co., 1965-1972 (Box 130, Folder 29)
- New York Joint Board, Local #400 and Rogers Peet Co., 1966-1976 (Box 130, Folder 30)
- New York Joint Board and Rogers Peet Co., 1981 (Box 130, Folder 31)
- Capitol District, Local #188 and Rogers Peet Co., 1962-1968 (Box 130, Folder 32)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and Perelmutter's (M. & L., Inc.), 1971-1977 (Box 130, Folder 33)
- New York Joint Board, Local #162 and Persall Tailors, 1980 (Box 130, Folder 34)
- Chicago Joint Board and Frank X Peter Co., Inc., 1977 (Box 130, Folder 35)
- California Joint Board and Howard & Gary Petersons, 1983 (Box 130, Folder 36)
- New England, Local #1069 and Pierce Mills Outlet, Weir Mills Outlet, East Providence Clothing Store, 1976 (Box 130, Folder 37)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Plymouth Hand Laundry, 1975 (Box 130, Folder 38)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Polacheck's Men's Clothing, 1977-1985 (Box 130, Folder 39)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board and Proudwinds, Inc. (Bond Stores), 1983-1986 (Box 130, Folder 40)
- General Office and Queens Knit Goods Processing Corp., 1963 (Box 130, Folder 41)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Clothing Workers Joint Board and R.G.N. Enterprises, Inc., 1985-1988 (Box 130, Folder 42)
- New York Joint Board and R&H Clothes, Inc., 1981 (Box 130, Folder 43)
- New York Joint Board and R.P. Clothing Enterprises, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box 130, Folder 44)
- New York Joint Board and Rare Breed, 1978-1981 (Box 130, Folder 45)
- Wisconsin, Local #80G and Reinhart Mitten Co., 1961-1965 (Box 130, Folder 46)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and Besse Richey, Inc., 1959-1965 (Box 130, Folder 47)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and Ripley Clothes, Inc., 1959 (Box 130, Folder 48)
- New York Joint Board and Arthur Rojack, Inc., 1975-1980 (Box 130, Folder 49)
- General Office and Ross Glove Co., 1961 (Box 130, Folder 50)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Royal Columbus Laundry, 1975 (Box 130, Folder 51)
- Local #340 and S. Fer International, Inc., 1988 (Box 130, Folder 52)
- Baltimore Regional Joint Board and Lewis and Thomas Saltz, 1983 (Box 130, Folder 53)
- Chicago Joint Board and Sandy's Dry Goods, 1973-1976 (Box 130, Folder 54)
- New York, Local #340A and Save-Now Discount Drugs, Inc., 1971 (Box 130, Folder 55)
- New York, Local #340A and Save-Rite Beauty Aids, Inc., 1970 (Box 130, Folder 56)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and Herman Schecter (Box 130, Folder 57)
- Chicago Joint Board and Schmitt-Orlow Stumpf's, 1977 (Box 130, Folder 58)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Robert E. Schmitz (The Hub and MacNeil & Purnell), 1985-1987 (Box 130, Folder 59)
- Philadelphia Joint Board and Scotese Bros., 1977 (Box 130, Folder 60)
- New York Joint Board and Moe Serchuck, 1978-1981 (Box 130, Folder 61)
- New England Regional Joint Board and Sergio, Inc. (Men at Large), 1974-1982 (Box 130, Folder 62)
- New York Joint Board and Shepard Clothes, 1978-1981 (Box 130, Folder 63)
- Chicago Joint Board and Sheboygan Drugs, Inc. (Union Prescription Centers), 1973-1974 (Box 130, Folder 64)
- Local #177 and Sherbrooke Sportswear Co., Inc., 1962 (Box 130, Folder 65)
- New York Joint Silver Brooks Fashions, Inc., 1981 (Box 130, Folder 66)
- Southern California Joint Board and F.B. Silverwood, 1977-1980 (Box 130, Folder 67)
- New York Joint Board and Sir Formal, Inc., 1971-1981 (Box 130, Folder 68)
- New England Regional Joint Board and Spartan Atlantic Division, Spartan Industries, 1969 (Box 130, Folder 69)
- Capitol District, Local #7 and Spector's Mens Clothing, 1977-1980 (Box 130, Folder 70)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Spoo & Son, 1985 (Box 130, Folder 71)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and State Bank of India, 1977 (Box 130, Folder 72)
- Chicago Joint Board and State Street Store Men's Department, 1973 (Box 130, Folder 73)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and Stephen's Men's World (Sullivan's, Inc.), 1962-1974 (Box 130, Folder 74)
- Chicago Joint Board and Stock Bros., Inc., 1977 (Box 131, Folder 1)
- Capitol District, Local #7 and Stulmakers, Ltd., 1975-1980 (Box 131, Folder 2)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers Union and Style Art Clothing Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 131, Folder 3)
- Chicago Joint Board and Style Shoe Store, 1973-1976 (Box 131, Folder 4)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers Union and Sutton Place Fashions, Inc., 1966 (Box 131, Folder 5)
- New England Regional Joint Board and the System Co., 1965-1980 (Box 131, Folder 6)
- New York Joint Board and Syms, Inc., 1978-1981 (Box 131, Folder 7)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board, Local #86 and The Tailor Shoppe (Robert Johnson), 1979 (Box 131, Folder 8)
- New York Joint Board and Tall Town of Huntington, Inc., 1981 (Box 131, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Ted-Mor Laundry, 1975 (Box 131, Folder 10)
- Chicago Joint Board and 10-X Manufacturing Co., 1973 (Box 131, Folder 11)
- Chicago Joint Board and Terry's Department Stores, Inc., 1965-1974 (Box 131, Folder 12)
- Boston Joint Board and Robert Todd, Ltd., Inc., 1973-1982 (Box 131, Folder 13)
- New York Joint Board and A Touch of Class for Men, Ltd., 1978 (Box 131, Folder 14)
- General Office and J. Leon Touro, Inc., 1971 (Box 131, Folder 15)
- Chicago Joint Board and Tram, Inc., 1975-1984 (Box 131, Folder 16)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers Union and Tri-National Glove Co., 1966-1972 (Box 131, Folder 17)
- New York, Local #252 and Triangle Bias Binding, 1938-1967 (Box 131, Folder 18)
- Joint Board of Shirt Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers Union and Trifles Co., 1983 (Box 131, Folder 19)
- Chicago Joint Board and Turner Clothes, 1973-1976 (Box 131, Folder 20)
- New York Joint Board and Turnpike Clothing Outlet, Inc., 1978 (Box 131, Folder 21)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Tweed Shop, Ltd., 1983 (Box 131, Folder 22)
- Midwest Regional Joint Board and 20th Century Glove Co., Inc., 1967 (Box 131, Folder 23)
- New York Joint Board and Twinnell Clothes, Inc., 1977 (Box 131, Folder 24)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Union Prescription Centers, Inc., 1987 (Box 131, Folder 25)
  2740 S 108th St West Allies, WI
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Union Prescription Centers, Inc., 1978-1984 (Box 131, Folder 26)
  709 W Oakland Ave Milwaukee, WI
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Union Prescription Centers, Inc., 1978-1987 (Box 131, Folder 27)
  3501 W Capitol Dr Milwaukee, WI
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Union Prescription Centers, Inc., 1981 (Box 131, Folder 28)
  501 E Main Street Watertown, WI
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Union Prescription Centers, Inc., 1978-1987 (Box 131, Folder 29)
  7206 W Greenfield West Allis, WI
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Union Prescription Centers, Inc., 1978-1987 (Box 131, Folder 30)
  4900 W North Ave Milwaukee, WI
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Universal Fabrics Co., Inc., 1974-1978 (Box 131, Folder 31)
- Lehigh Valley Joint Board and Universal Pants, 1963-1971 (Box 131, Folder 32)
- Capitol District, Local #188 and University Shop, 1960-1975 (Box 131, Folder 33)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and V & V Custom Tailors, 1977 (Box 131, Folder 34)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and Vestuti & Villecco, 1965-1977 (Box 131, Folder 35)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers Union and Victor Gloves Manufacturing Corp., 1966-1976 (Box 131, Folder 36)
- Joint Board of Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove and Rainwear Workers Union and Viva Creations, Inc., 1977 (Box 131, Folder 37)
- New York Joint Board and Walker & Florio, 1975-1980 (Box 131, Folder 38)
- Massachusetts, Local #579 and Ware Pratt Co., 1967-1971 (Box 131, Folder 39)
- New York Joint Board and Watermill Enterprises, Inc., 1965 (Box 131, Folder 40)
- Northeast Regional Organization, Local #382 and Warwick Valley Manufacturing Co., 1962 (Box 131, Folder 41)
- Local #187 and Weyland Manufacturing Co., 1965 (Box 131, Folder 42)
- Massachusetts, Local #174 and Wear Well Trouser Co., 1954-1976 (Box 131, Folder 43)
- General Office and Wells-Lamont Corp., 1956-1961 (Box 131, Folder 44)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Wend Bend Prescription Center, Ltd. (Union Prescript Center, Inc.), 1981-1984 (Box 131, Folder 45)
- New York, Local #340A and Whelan Drug Co., Inc. (Sav-On, Inc.), 1971 (Box 131, Folder 46)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and White, Inc., 1965-1977 (Box 131, Folder 47)
- Chicago and Central States Joint Board and Whiting Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1980 (Box 131, Folder 48)
- Capitol District, Local #188 and Joseph A. Wilner, Co., 1960-1983 (Box 131, Folder 49)
- New York Joint Board and Wind Shaper Madison Corp., 1981 (Box 131, Folder 50)
- New England, Local #382 and Winsor Manufacturing Co., 1966 (Box 131, Folder 51)
- Midwest, Local #66 and Wolens Trouser Co., 1956-1965 (Box 131, Folder 52)
- Connecticut, Local #115 and Wolf's, Inc., 1965-1972 (Box 131, Folder 53)
- Massachusetts, Local #174 and Worcester Pants Co., 1958-1961 (Box 131, Folder 54)
- Southern California Joint Board and Zodys, 1968-1982 (Box 131, Folder 55)
- Amalgamated Service and Allied Industries and Able Cleaning Contractors, Inc., 1989 (Box 132, Folder 1)
- Southern California Joint Board and Zachary All, 1977 (Box 132, Folder 2)
- New England Regional Joint Board, Local #177 and Anderson-Little Co. (Richman Bros. Co.), 1965-1990 (Box 132, Folder 3)
- New England Tailors Joint Board and Anderson-Little Co., 1977 (Box 132, Folder 4)
- New York Joint Board and Appel, Brooks & Webber Uniform, 1975-1982 (Box 132, Folder 5)
- Southern California Joint Board, Local #55D and Ardens of Compton, CA, 1970 (Box 132, Folder 6)
- Southern California Joint Board, Local #55D and Ardens of La Miranda, CA, 1970 (Box 132, Folder 7)
- Southern California Joint Board, Local #55D and Ardens of Montebello, CA, 1970 (Box 132, Folder 8)
- Toronto Joint Board and Arrow Uniform, Inc., 1986-1989 (Box 132, Folder 9)
- California Joint Board and Arthurs, 1983 (Box 132, Folder 10)
- New York Joint Board and Best Uniform Co., Inc., 1980-1982 (Box 132, Folder 11)
- Pennsylvania Joint Board and Big Yank Corp., 1965-1990 (Box 132, Folder 12)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board and Big Yank Corp., 1966-1988 (Box 132, Folder 13)
- New York Joint Board and Bobcraft Fashion Clothes, Inc., 1977-1982 (Box 132, Folder 14)
- New York Joint Board and J. Borah & Co., Inc., 1977-1982 (Box 132, Folder 15)
- Western Ontario Joint Board, Local #573 and Bradshaw-Stradwick, Inc., 1976-1986 (Box 132, Folder 16)
- New York Joint Board and Brooks Brothers, 1971-1984 (Box 132, Folder 17)